let questions = [
  {
    "numb": 61,
    "question": "Hierarchy emerges almost inevitably through a wide variety of evolutionary processes, for the simple reason that hierarchical structures are _____ (fill in the blank)",
    "answer": "stable",
    "options": ["perfect", "imperfect", "stable", "unstable"]
  },
  {
    "numb": 62,
    "question": "Which of these is a stochastic factor",
    "answer": "environmental fluctuation",
    "options": ["birth rate", "death rate", "population structure", "environmental fluctuation"]
  },
  {
    "numb": 63,
    "question": "The climax near Tindi village is being controlled by disturbance by cattle. This is an example of",
    "answer": "disclimax",
    "options": ["climatic climax", "edaphic climax", "disclimax", "catastrophic climax"]
  },
  {
    "numb": 64,
    "question": "_____ determines which projects or developments require a full or partial impact assessment study (fill in the blank)",
    "answer": "screening",
    "options": ["screening", "scoping", "reporting", "review"]
  },
  {
    "numb": 65,
    "question": "The movement of lions across the Gir landscape is an example of",
    "answer": "diffusion",
    "options": ["diffusion", "secular dispersal", "jump dispersal", "drifting"]
  },
  {
    "numb": 66,
    "question": "Trampling of grass due to the movement of animals is an example of",
    "answer": "amensalism",
    "options": ["mutualism", "amensalism", "commensalism", "protocooperation"]
  },
  {
    "numb": 67,
    "question": "Cover board surveys are typically used for sampling",
    "answer": "herpetofauna",
    "options": ["herpetofauna", "fishes", "large mammals", "carnivores"]
  },
  {
    "numb": 68,
    "question": "Glacial lakes are typical examples of",
    "answer": "oligotrophic lakes",
    "options": ["eutrophic lakes", "hypereutrophic lakes", "oligotrophic lakes", "mesotrophic lakes"]
  },
  {
    "numb": 69,
    "question": "Which of these is not a climatic forcing for Earth",
    "answer": "change in sun's orbit",
    "options": ["change in plates tectonics", "change in earth's orbit", "change is sun's orbit", "change in sun's strength"]
  },
  {
    "numb": 70,
    "question": "Which of these is not a characteristic of fitness",
    "answer": "higher reproductive rate means higher fitness",
    "options": ["fitness is environmental specific", "fitness if species specific", "higher reproductive rate means higher fitness", "fitness should be measured across several generations"]
  }]